yes definitely I think this is like a
testament you know to the work that we
have done and in showcasing our vision
of changing the way people feel about
insurance
and um we always you know encourage over
people to have like Innovative on my
side to know about my side and also give
our people the opportunities you know to
join our Journeys to improve our product
and services and this is why Dei is very
important for our people and
organization because these are our
people to think differently and also
respect the differences which we you
know believe that this will make FWD a
great place to work and last but not
least this award recognized our key
myself and serve you know as a reminder
to keep up working hard you know um to
make FWD a great place to work
well I would like to step back a bit you
know during video like the engagement
assessment survey was actually asked us
to know the question regarding to core
sales and also the group you know about
part my soul thing to act you know
Escape out the opportunity to listen to
our employee and and understand what is
over cause right you know that to keep
us continue working and the area that we
should do it better to make it more
impact to our employees and you know
from that stage to today tonight we
actually you know I'm surrounded by
people and companies you know where they
share the same goals you know and we can
learn from their practice we can learn
you know from their sharing anything
together you know we can create a better
impact not actually individual level
organization level but for our society
and Community as well thank you
foreign